{"instructions": ["This section is an extended version of previous task, which is clicking on the <strong>WORD</strong> prompted by the voice. <p></p>In cases where you can not hear the word, just give your best guess.", "When you are ready, click <strong>Continue</strong> to hear the first word."], "feedback": true, "holdfeedback": false, "feedbackdur": 600, "serveraudio": false, "estimatedduration": 4, "randomize": false, "isi": 600, "volume": [{"plugin": "html-button-response", "prompt": "Let us adjust the volume one more time for louder sounds. Please lower down your volume first.", "choices": ["Continue"]}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Now adjust your computer volume up to a comfortable (but not too loud) level.", "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/volume.wav", "choices": ["I have adjusted the volume, let's continue"]}, {"plugin": "html-button-response", "prompt": "Is the right headphone in your right ear, and the left headphone in your left ear? It is very important!", "choices": ["Yes, let's continue."]}], "trials": [{"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["must", "bust", "gust", "rust", "dust", "just"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-space_-10_6_4_BjBO0FPVAUyIC3Qk.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "echo-space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["coil", "oil", "soil", "toil", "boil", "foil"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/pitch_-6_23_4_1Wr92o6hdJAMQKQX.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-6", "condition": "pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pat", "pad", "pan", "path", "pack", "pass"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/ref_-6_3_3_ZEkml0xIhod3nxzD.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-6", "condition": "ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["not", "tot", "got", "pot", "hot", "lot"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/space_6_14_6_L18RqAC9vocFzPaf.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "6", "condition": "space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["thaw", "law", "raw", "paw", "jaw", "saw"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/space_-6_31_5_QGbiFoGeQI8zYr9N.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-6", "condition": "space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pin", "sin", "tin", "fin", "din", "win"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-sum_2_10_4_uo5I6uwndTTtjWB3.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "echo-sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["kill", "kin", "kit", "kick", "king", "kid"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-ref_2_37_3_plRsoSX3huzGolpe.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["peace", "peas", "peak", "peach", "peat", "peal"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-sum_8_47_5_0SsGIlB2cTg3vWmP.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "echo-sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pat", "pad", "pan", "path", "pack", "pass"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/sum_5_3_2_ipsSs2yGIgnjlHgY.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "5", "condition": "sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["peel", "reel", "feel", "eel", "keel", "heel"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/anechoic_2_27_6_v3xavKoTprM8hFDM.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "anechoic"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["wick", "sick", "kick", "lick", "pick", "tick"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-pitch_-4_46_5_Gc0JR90CbAH7ZBzY.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "echo-pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["lane", "lay", "late", "lake", "lace", "lame"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-noise_14_4_6_dHNCExl1VHlTAeto.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo-noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["bale", "gale", "sale", "tale", "pale", "male"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/noise_12_45_1_nHbv5cZZwHl3dNnu.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "12", "condition": "noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["bun", "bus", "but", "bug", "buck", "buff"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-space_8_48_6_IK3n18GWOsyuWYfV.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "echo-space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pale", "pace", "page", "pane", "pay", "pave"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-space_14_20_4_PvizrAq89fpP5fYO.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo-space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["back", "bath", "bad", "bass", "bat", "ban"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-space_8_17_1_6jThJp7EAT38tsMF.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "echo-space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["took", "cook", "look", "hook", "shook", "book"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-pitch_2_39_5_X2z10Ng32AwWer4J.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "echo-pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["went", "sent", "bent", "dent", "tent", "rent"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/space_12_1_5_RWvImw1Ua5PQyLd1.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "12", "condition": "space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pig", "pill", "pin", "pip", "pit", "pick"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-pitch_-10_16_3_HZTS7AFA8Mv26rJS.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "echo-pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["din", "dill", "dim", "dig", "dip", "did"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-space_2_8_5_24w28BOj72y1tbsA.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "echo-space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["thaw", "law", "raw", "paw", "jaw", "saw"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-pitch_14_31_3_iYqQXzvgxsV0o1DH.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo-pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["way", "may", "say", "pay", "day", "gay"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-ref_-4_18_4_stLQusPXaa44KrqF.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["din", "dill", "dim", "dig", "dip", "did"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/ref_6_8_1_zRNT5I7ss4VtyZ91.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "6", "condition": "ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["mass", "math", "map", "mat", "man", "mad"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-ref_2_40_3_IjUpEzxPwBHFCb91.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["way", "may", "say", "pay", "day", "gay"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-space_-10_18_3_dRf1AiKtbEqA67Zo.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "echo-space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["same", "name", "game", "tame", "came", "fame"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-ref_14_26_1_m6WfPY21Ix2lJ4Bf.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["not", "tot", "got", "pot", "hot", "lot"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-sum_-10_14_3_zqeyamzCE018W2qa.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "echo-sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["back", "bath", "bad", "bass", "bat", "ban"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/noise_5_17_4_VvVXwZSoc6STDhdP.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "5", "condition": "noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["seep", "seen", "seethe", "seek", "seem", "seed"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-noise_-7_13_3_EBiQGOkUkhrSHWpA.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-7", "condition": "echo-noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["puff", "puck", "pub", "pus", "pup", "pun"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-space_8_33_6_xJFqtFtOwHnR5CUv.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "echo-space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["bean", "beach", "beat", "beak", "bead", "beam"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/sum_12_34_1_ftMJFubVZRWf6uLc.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "12", "condition": "sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["bale", "gale", "sale", "tale", "pale", "male"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-sum_8_45_2_E6VYPAW04gCXx9gq.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "echo-sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["mass", "math", "map", "mat", "man", "mad"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-pitch_2_40_2_UyrA8OGBAYhZTPTC.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "echo-pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["dip", "sip", "hip", "tip", "lip", "rip"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/ref_-12_36_5_NnGPMUDOJAxASIAx.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-12", "condition": "ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["fit", "fib", "fizz", "fill", "fig", "fin"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-sum_8_25_1_Gn2BuhpA9687kUWj.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "echo-sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["ray", "raze", "rate", "rave", "rake", "race"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/noise_-2_41_3_w5F6E6zzK6LdjZhf.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-2", "condition": "noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pale", "pace", "page", "pane", "pay", "pave"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/pitch_6_20_3_U1I7ybhRD8qDSQr7.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "6", "condition": "pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["sum", "sun", "sung", "sup", "sub", "sud"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-noise_14_12_5_86vPwhWnY8BK1Fuj.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo-noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["sum", "sun", "sung", "sup", "sub", "sud"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-sum_-10_12_4_njLyB26RygPEKt7g.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "echo-sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["same", "name", "game", "tame", "came", "fame"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/pitch_-12_26_6_Vnrkl4rVTUSWZTb0.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-12", "condition": "pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["puff", "puck", "pub", "pus", "pup", "pun"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/space_6_33_5_YudYfknCmGhiaDRu.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "6", "condition": "space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["way", "may", "say", "pay", "day", "gay"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/pitch_-12_18_1_5QV7LUmOkwtI3d9R.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-12", "condition": "pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["cane", "case", "cape", "cake", "came", "cave"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-sum_-4_21_1_0LDapHTM3B80wnln.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "echo-sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["same", "name", "game", "tame", "came", "fame"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-noise_-7_26_6_YL0oonW9KXLnzGn1.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-7", "condition": "echo-noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["wick", "sick", "kick", "lick", "pick", "tick"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/sum_12_46_3_8piWZTYG0putIbLj.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "12", "condition": "sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["bean", "beach", "beat", "beak", "bead", "beam"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/noise_-16_34_2_smpp5s8FvNEcMiPB.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-16", "condition": "noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["din", "dill", "dim", "dig", "dip", "did"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/anechoic_8_8_1_NNoi1CKtDz2hWodt.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "anechoic"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["lane", "lay", "late", "lake", "lace", "lame"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/ref_-12_4_1_pZSqwDYFlhGUNKOu.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-12", "condition": "ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["bed", "led", "fed", "red", "wed", "shed"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-ref_8_9_4_sFiwHbbTsTPX1ucn.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["coil", "oil", "soil", "toil", "boil", "foil"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/noise_5_23_6_4jwbBffxYxSqr1NF.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "5", "condition": "noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["mass", "math", "map", "mat", "man", "mad"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/anechoic_-10_40_3_aNvjjvu21BHTboHT.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "anechoic"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["puff", "puck", "pub", "pus", "pup", "pun"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-ref_-4_33_6_5ngbxUax3jqKTlt0.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["bun", "bus", "but", "bug", "buck", "buff"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-pitch_-4_48_5_8ALbRtcUkGeMJucl.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "echo-pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["coil", "oil", "soil", "toil", "boil", "foil"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/ref_-12_23_2_LCzfqcWYtsxkiTi3.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-12", "condition": "ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["tan", "tang", "tap", "tack", "tam", "tab"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-pitch_14_24_2_rUFXWA3hICe8gyEU.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo-pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["cane", "case", "cape", "cake", "came", "cave"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-space_-4_21_3_P6yPt3TAPbMWxktt.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "echo-space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["bed", "led", "fed", "red", "wed", "shed"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/anechoic_14_9_5_INSgyCv2pUYqgHQT.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "anechoic"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["cup", "cut", "cud", "cuff", "cuss", "cub"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-noise_7_30_4_UMrCiSlhDZWLXPOn.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "7", "condition": "echo-noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["fun", "sun", "bun", "gun", "run", "nun"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-pitch_8_50_4_wLxsdoqEYdnbI7Zj.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "echo-pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["went", "sent", "bent", "dent", "tent", "rent"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/noise_-16_1_6_MQz8agZzmuermCVW.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-16", "condition": "noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["sill", "sick", "sip", "sing", "sit", "sin"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/pitch_0_44_6_kEfRtkX3eCupS6DD.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "0", "condition": "pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["sum", "sun", "sung", "sup", "sub", "sud"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/ref_0_12_3_h8KAEaRkqdoIuj8X.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "0", "condition": "ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["fit", "fib", "fizz", "fill", "fig", "fin"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/noise_-2_25_3_NcZ37dDHhQk1vHXp.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-2", "condition": "noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["dip", "sip", "hip", "tip", "lip", "rip"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/noise_-16_36_1_sAwnhIp0VRHUtuD7.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-16", "condition": "noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["sill", "sick", "sip", "sing", "sit", "sin"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/noise_12_44_5_r61Ua5bNqGSWhrp9.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "12", "condition": "noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["sag", "sat", "sass", "sack", "sad", "sap"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/sum_12_49_5_ocXo3d5f2f1YhXLQ.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "12", "condition": "sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["way", "may", "say", "pay", "day", "gay"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-sum_-4_18_1_VuVENsi050RHemP8.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "echo-sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["dip", "sip", "hip", "tip", "lip", "rip"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo_2_36_1_fmJkEoXS11bHA5Vh.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "echo"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["fit", "fib", "fizz", "fill", "fig", "fin"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-ref_8_25_4_JX77Z4OE99rS5Fq6.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["seep", "seen", "seethe", "seek", "seem", "seed"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-pitch_-10_13_1_FEPNgW8OdocnuyyV.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "echo-pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["coil", "oil", "soil", "toil", "boil", "foil"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-sum_14_23_6_PP4na8gCCFsyKgTu.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo-sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["vest", "test", "rest", "best", "west", "nest"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/anechoic_-10_15_5_SQkh5yAYDqhQJ2UB.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "anechoic"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["fun", "sun", "bun", "gun", "run", "nun"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo_2_50_4_xOIOPSImWGfbKTWU.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "echo"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pale", "pace", "page", "pane", "pay", "pave"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo_-4_20_3_rwIKwrcSvQ24lBoi.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "echo"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["puff", "puck", "pub", "pus", "pup", "pun"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-pitch_8_33_2_DFNdIoduSxWWIAl8.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "echo-pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pin", "sin", "tin", "fin", "din", "win"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/space_6_10_1_GJrt1HkrVanZtY24.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "6", "condition": "space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["bean", "beach", "beat", "beak", "bead", "beam"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/sum_5_34_1_F3ONLoR4fnA5xN7s.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "5", "condition": "sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["peace", "peas", "peak", "peach", "peat", "peal"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/pitch_6_47_2_MFymyvy9mHTEXVnL.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "6", "condition": "pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["din", "dill", "dim", "dig", "dip", "did"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-noise_-7_8_1_gbpgHydVqV4QDvu5.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-7", "condition": "echo-noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["fit", "fib", "fizz", "fill", "fig", "fin"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/sum_-9_25_1_JeXX4SZ4YNzSSY65.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-9", "condition": "sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["hold", "cold", "told", "fold", "sold", "gold"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-space_2_2_2_upssswMDAwSqqhCe.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "echo-space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["sill", "sick", "sip", "sing", "sit", "sin"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-sum_-10_44_5_OY7bq9uPMk987wz0.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "echo-sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["ray", "raze", "rate", "rave", "rake", "race"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo_8_41_3_3igVOqX85mnQudAB.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "echo"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["fun", "sun", "bun", "gun", "run", "nun"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/sum_5_50_4_vOLU2BZDF2Q8PAFW.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "5", "condition": "sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["teak", "team", "teal", "teach", "tear", "tease"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/space_-12_7_2_fY5BGWdN9GXTwkFC.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-12", "condition": "space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["heave", "hear", "heat", "heal", "heap", "heath"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-ref_8_29_6_Pkii61skZHKYU8DM.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["cane", "case", "cape", "cake", "came", "cave"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-noise_-14_21_2_tDS4J27MNKOIIFf9.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-14", "condition": "echo-noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pig", "big", "dig", "wig", "rig", "fig"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/pitch_0_19_4_2rtYtfoVfbkSpdel.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "0", "condition": "pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["shop", "mop", "cop", "top", "hop", "pop"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/ref_0_22_5_bcX2YG5iPqGcGKtg.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "0", "condition": "ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["teak", "team", "teal", "teach", "tear", "tease"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/sum_-2_7_4_7bUtT6uH4Ckmjj8U.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-2", "condition": "sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["not", "tot", "got", "pot", "hot", "lot"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/sum_-9_14_2_MiPdIYZzuPznVRyK.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-9", "condition": "sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["seep", "seen", "seethe", "seek", "seem", "seed"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-pitch_14_13_4_rJ4PLMrVuWM4H1ds.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo-pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["fill", "kill", "will", "hill", "till", "bill"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-sum_8_43_1_93ijlIpl2TFEFDdR.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "echo-sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["seep", "seen", "seethe", "seek", "seem", "seed"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo_2_13_1_O2UWjALMAJ4eXDIs.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "echo"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["heave", "hear", "heat", "heal", "heap", "heath"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-noise_7_29_6_yyVr1nqog15mWd21.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "7", "condition": "echo-noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pen", "hen", "men", "then", "den", "ten"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-noise_14_32_2_tXsFrJjzH76oeT5U.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo-noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["kill", "kin", "kit", "kick", "king", "kid"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-sum_2_37_4_As5B2r9nQoRnDP6S.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "echo-sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["dug", "dung", "duck", "dud", "dub", "dun"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo_2_11_5_Ni9H7n00dS0p55aE.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "echo"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["hang", "sang", "bang", "rang", "fang", "gang"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/space_12_38_2_VwxGT7eAVioh5z08.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "12", "condition": "space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["hang", "sang", "bang", "rang", "fang", "gang"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-noise_7_38_4_lQ1tadhPsTUUl4VV.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "7", "condition": "echo-noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["tan", "tang", "tap", "tack", "tam", "tab"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-noise_-7_24_4_ifVFTyssREXc5sRn.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-7", "condition": "echo-noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["back", "bath", "bad", "bass", "bat", "ban"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/space_-6_17_4_4LMm7WlRKRsd0EXv.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-6", "condition": "space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pen", "hen", "men", "then", "den", "ten"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/ref_-6_32_2_SxTsesuGxUdhsvV1.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-6", "condition": "ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["hark", "dark", "mark", "bark", "park", "lark"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/anechoic_8_28_2_kNFw2GFS6Ls9jqNH.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "anechoic"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["tan", "tang", "tap", "tack", "tam", "tab"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/sum_-2_24_6_4qAEg2O5h66BEK1c.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-2", "condition": "sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["heave", "hear", "heat", "heal", "heap", "heath"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/sum_-16_29_3_pFzy0fKQvtYQb05O.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-16", "condition": "sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["back", "bath", "bad", "bass", "bat", "ban"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/noise_-9_17_5_kHbdbJmBUwJBTz0S.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-9", "condition": "noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["din", "dill", "dim", "dig", "dip", "did"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-noise_0_8_2_SIdl85tIp5ONFS0A.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "0", "condition": "echo-noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["heat", "neat", "feat", "seat", "meat", "beat"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-sum_2_35_5_dyJHqt8b4zJ4n8gQ.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "echo-sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["cup", "cut", "cud", "cuff", "cuss", "cub"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo_14_30_5_4vvC24hPQ8kznq3I.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pen", "hen", "men", "then", "den", "ten"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-sum_14_32_3_pL27pdl1NUkwLoL2.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo-sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pat", "pad", "pan", "path", "pack", "pass"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-sum_14_3_6_yRmVqEcxkjNNBusN.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo-sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["bean", "beach", "beat", "beak", "bead", "beam"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/anechoic_2_34_6_W5i1HPagfdcHgll6.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "anechoic"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["bean", "beach", "beat", "beak", "bead", "beam"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-ref_-10_34_1_2GYkRNo4zuF0DDVH.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["wick", "sick", "kick", "lick", "pick", "tick"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/sum_-2_46_1_8EdUZ8t9yOANiKHE.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-2", "condition": "sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["fun", "sun", "bun", "gun", "run", "nun"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/anechoic_-4_50_6_MjvqcmY6Ez6jEdV0.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "anechoic"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["hold", "cold", "told", "fold", "sold", "gold"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/ref_0_2_6_sCTx6bWCRqiNK1n0.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "0", "condition": "ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["dug", "dung", "duck", "dud", "dub", "dun"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-noise_-14_11_2_IXF8sdbGosjJP82O.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-14", "condition": "echo-noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["way", "may", "say", "pay", "day", "gay"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-space_-4_18_6_5PkpOmvBIY17FH9z.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "echo-space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["took", "cook", "look", "hook", "shook", "book"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/anechoic_-4_39_3_1XMdwlGjKnkKbax2.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "anechoic"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["heat", "neat", "feat", "seat", "meat", "beat"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-ref_-4_35_5_PeajjA7E7v0AzZRT.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["teak", "team", "teal", "teach", "tear", "tease"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/sum_-16_7_5_hC6MyWPAXs1dIiVT.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-16", "condition": "sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["kill", "kin", "kit", "kick", "king", "kid"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-space_14_37_6_lcP8aBJygosoACFX.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo-space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["teak", "team", "teal", "teach", "tear", "tease"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo_14_7_1_K5vRRmsNzn42ZRLb.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["mass", "math", "map", "mat", "man", "mad"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-noise_7_40_4_9LxCndn4ns3igzKC.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "7", "condition": "echo-noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["tan", "tang", "tap", "tack", "tam", "tab"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo_-4_24_2_vIXUTruUJml2o8n1.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "echo"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["fill", "kill", "will", "hill", "till", "bill"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/anechoic_-10_43_1_YVeJ75hd0JFuQAB6.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "anechoic"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["took", "cook", "look", "hook", "shook", "book"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-ref_-10_39_1_PUeD1fpvwbbIxmRP.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["not", "tot", "got", "pot", "hot", "lot"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/sum_-9_14_6_fB7HAbhPBCMos9jk.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-9", "condition": "sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["bale", "gale", "sale", "tale", "pale", "male"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-space_14_45_3_ArvZ1CRdKnx1GLM8.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo-space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["seep", "seen", "seethe", "seek", "seem", "seed"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo_-10_13_3_l400p0LNyg6OAHta.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "echo"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["thaw", "law", "raw", "paw", "jaw", "saw"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/sum_5_31_3_hI0OeG6jrCjq9AzQ.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "5", "condition": "sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["peel", "reel", "feel", "eel", "keel", "heel"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/anechoic_-4_27_2_uENqu0DtvuusK70V.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "anechoic"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["thaw", "law", "raw", "paw", "jaw", "saw"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo_14_31_6_qPegJMltkq5zF1BF.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["fill", "kill", "will", "hill", "till", "bill"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/space_12_43_5_9nhLup2cNr0eLU0H.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "12", "condition": "space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["must", "bust", "gust", "rust", "dust", "just"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-space_2_6_5_fRchFzAmuVtCy4n6.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "echo-space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["peel", "reel", "feel", "eel", "keel", "heel"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/noise_-2_27_4_pRiqRg2ZW21cpygS.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-2", "condition": "noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pen", "hen", "men", "then", "den", "ten"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/pitch_6_32_1_DIvBdWrH4t32PMkM.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "6", "condition": "pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["not", "tot", "got", "pot", "hot", "lot"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/anechoic_14_14_4_jxJfl2QbXAc9nJy9.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "anechoic"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["hang", "sang", "bang", "rang", "fang", "gang"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/pitch_0_38_2_lKmjyYXpIsSvWImj.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "0", "condition": "pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["thaw", "law", "raw", "paw", "jaw", "saw"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo_-10_31_2_tyOgBHTQs0w06ttf.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "echo"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["fit", "fib", "fizz", "fill", "fig", "fin"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo_-4_25_4_HzuYMK4RDNiyJTnT.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "echo"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["cane", "case", "cape", "cake", "came", "cave"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/noise_12_21_5_MM1zEAdIAyiVhfIr.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "12", "condition": "noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["bed", "led", "fed", "red", "wed", "shed"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-pitch_-10_9_6_0zPfQxbjev8jhuUv.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "echo-pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["must", "bust", "gust", "rust", "dust", "just"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/noise_12_6_5_1L3a1jNe7Vx7KPsE.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "12", "condition": "noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["save", "same", "sale", "sane", "sake", "safe"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-ref_14_42_2_RFyzr8z6Sd26Q4xI.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["kit", "bit", "fit", "hit", "wit", "sit"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-noise_0_5_1_zvMZZPBT4FECF1C7.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "0", "condition": "echo-noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["sag", "sat", "sass", "sack", "sad", "sap"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo_8_49_5_EidzsxO6EkmjMAUu.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "echo"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["hark", "dark", "mark", "bark", "park", "lark"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/noise_-16_28_4_JufC7ylaYTcUiEcV.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-16", "condition": "noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pin", "sin", "tin", "fin", "din", "win"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-space_2_10_1_39bboexfhmk6r74f.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "echo-space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["teak", "team", "teal", "teach", "tear", "tease"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/ref_6_7_1_jSqAJlHCVQUsBArb.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "6", "condition": "ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["fill", "kill", "will", "hill", "till", "bill"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/anechoic_2_43_5_eWC2hS4xkYQYck8H.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "anechoic"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["wick", "sick", "kick", "lick", "pick", "tick"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-noise_0_46_1_JLWlODh3aYBoNuSs.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "0", "condition": "echo-noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["cane", "case", "cape", "cake", "came", "cave"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/sum_-16_21_4_TEJyVz9Wp3Fp1j6U.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-16", "condition": "sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["save", "same", "sale", "sane", "sake", "safe"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/anechoic_14_42_6_o4jSbnqteAE5LrhC.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "anechoic"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["dug", "dung", "duck", "dud", "dub", "dun"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/sum_-16_11_6_EfXJaqrcjl9Uj56B.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-16", "condition": "sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["hark", "dark", "mark", "bark", "park", "lark"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/pitch_0_28_5_999cZQgIrNa4iQji.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "0", "condition": "pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["fun", "sun", "bun", "gun", "run", "nun"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-ref_-4_50_5_shwFEtRiYZwEDPwS.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pale", "pace", "page", "pane", "pay", "pave"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-space_-10_20_1_YrzN4bYgupOIYd9H.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "echo-space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["bed", "led", "fed", "red", "wed", "shed"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/pitch_-6_9_3_aRQGMz5rDugVdlba.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-6", "condition": "pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["bean", "beach", "beat", "beak", "bead", "beam"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-pitch_-10_34_6_peKg1FbxRUw8rGNz.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "echo-pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["heat", "neat", "feat", "seat", "meat", "beat"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/pitch_-6_35_3_zhVypQev88jCG7vn.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-6", "condition": "pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["kill", "kin", "kit", "kick", "king", "kid"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/noise_-9_37_2_YpNNTD2Bb8WeiMwP.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-9", "condition": "noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["kit", "bit", "fit", "hit", "wit", "sit"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-sum_-10_5_4_GumhscKcRrbCHRsp.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "echo-sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["bale", "gale", "sale", "tale", "pale", "male"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/anechoic_-10_45_6_WF9OVwoJjfjxBtiB.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "anechoic"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["hang", "sang", "bang", "rang", "fang", "gang"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-sum_14_38_2_3hw6KlQUoO7iB6Jv.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo-sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pat", "pad", "pan", "path", "pack", "pass"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/space_-12_3_4_EkATtcK8xsFLLta4.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-12", "condition": "space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["cup", "cut", "cud", "cuff", "cuss", "cub"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/ref_12_30_3_uaOlgyZuj0KyQu3P.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "12", "condition": "ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["dip", "sip", "hip", "tip", "lip", "rip"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/sum_-9_36_6_bLBwtXJe3UC6olEh.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-9", "condition": "sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["sum", "sun", "sung", "sup", "sub", "sud"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/pitch_-12_12_5_1uTthGd6QNVDqL0m.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-12", "condition": "pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["went", "sent", "bent", "dent", "tent", "rent"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/pitch_12_1_4_FiBvosSUH9U6BCiD.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "12", "condition": "pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pig", "big", "dig", "wig", "rig", "fig"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/ref_6_19_4_caIuuVUJBTo0OAGN.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "6", "condition": "ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["same", "name", "game", "tame", "came", "fame"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/ref_-6_26_2_F4Gd0OLSRsVKKnbi.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-6", "condition": "ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["vest", "test", "rest", "best", "west", "nest"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/pitch_-6_15_6_CJZTDKjlWPOGPxZ8.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-6", "condition": "pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["back", "bath", "bad", "bass", "bat", "ban"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-ref_2_17_6_Fy4UW9uNKYbO1ZEv.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pin", "sin", "tin", "fin", "din", "win"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo_14_10_1_OkxNuY4zd2Jhdv0U.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["lane", "lay", "late", "lake", "lace", "lame"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/ref_-6_4_2_knzVyo0hySZiIoHy.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-6", "condition": "ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["shop", "mop", "cop", "top", "hop", "pop"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-pitch_8_22_1_JvsdObMNurIwnk3u.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "echo-pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["dug", "dung", "duck", "dud", "dub", "dun"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-space_-4_11_4_DrRV8UHFsIdTGIxX.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "echo-space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["peel", "reel", "feel", "eel", "keel", "heel"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/ref_12_27_3_ks5t6twY6E7EXqWB.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "12", "condition": "ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["hark", "dark", "mark", "bark", "park", "lark"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-space_8_28_3_ZN4CxHbUgf0kg42m.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "echo-space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["hark", "dark", "mark", "bark", "park", "lark"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/anechoic_8_28_6_sY7smlPbvLx48uH3.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "anechoic"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["sag", "sat", "sass", "sack", "sad", "sap"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo_-10_49_4_j2nVKRfBrNlA7XvE.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "echo"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["bun", "bus", "but", "bug", "buck", "buff"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-noise_-14_48_3_uxPyaw26Np2am7XX.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-14", "condition": "echo-noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pig", "pill", "pin", "pip", "pit", "pick"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/sum_-2_16_1_axRuvjslnaQ0HR0J.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-2", "condition": "sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["dip", "sip", "hip", "tip", "lip", "rip"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/pitch_-12_36_4_gK9UGdBPZDAXrX3E.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-12", "condition": "pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["took", "cook", "look", "hook", "shook", "book"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/space_-12_39_2_i4uTR1IG4ebmhnju.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-12", "condition": "space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["vest", "test", "rest", "best", "west", "nest"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/ref_0_15_6_BO12UYyocrWZbERx.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "0", "condition": "ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pig", "big", "dig", "wig", "rig", "fig"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/space_0_19_1_7h7vjLqzRbq9eoRA.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "0", "condition": "space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["peace", "peas", "peak", "peach", "peat", "peal"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-sum_2_47_1_ZSnLTU4Fs3GjRsYq.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "echo-sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["save", "same", "sale", "sane", "sake", "safe"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/space_0_42_6_hbuzropOHkexal5f.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "0", "condition": "space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["bed", "led", "fed", "red", "wed", "shed"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-pitch_-4_9_2_nIyTywziaVdTdIZp.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "echo-pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["shop", "mop", "cop", "top", "hop", "pop"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-ref_2_22_1_HiIhoQELMF7paaGs.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["kit", "bit", "fit", "hit", "wit", "sit"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-pitch_-4_5_5_xYZYG3th5tmWqEM6.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "echo-pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["vest", "test", "rest", "best", "west", "nest"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-space_-10_15_6_9Qn4EVQG5eZjqMVF.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "echo-space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pig", "big", "dig", "wig", "rig", "fig"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo_8_19_1_eROOBo0J39PAjjSc.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "echo"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["sag", "sat", "sass", "sack", "sad", "sap"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/ref_12_49_3_A0yE6UUliSUZShjl.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "12", "condition": "ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["heave", "hear", "heat", "heal", "heap", "heath"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/space_-12_29_2_WEPBGfkzIqdLv0Kh.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-12", "condition": "space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["fill", "kill", "will", "hill", "till", "bill"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-ref_14_43_3_oqhOZCCkjC8eEmFC.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["hold", "cold", "told", "fold", "sold", "gold"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-sum_-4_2_6_I3PlXhkpo3OUM3YE.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "echo-sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pig", "big", "dig", "wig", "rig", "fig"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-space_14_19_3_2zzLeoCevbYGKzcC.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo-space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["fit", "fib", "fizz", "fill", "fig", "fin"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/space_0_25_2_EW7wL3FaGqqlZ3Zc.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "0", "condition": "space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["kit", "bit", "fit", "hit", "wit", "sit"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-ref_-10_5_2_9XGIldZvBcPbBmR2.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["puff", "puck", "pub", "pus", "pup", "pun"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/ref_-12_33_2_f2t8yN7Om94SoHAl.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-12", "condition": "ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["hold", "cold", "told", "fold", "sold", "gold"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/anechoic_8_2_6_jDpPoRCKOBUCLGQk.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "anechoic"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pin", "sin", "tin", "fin", "din", "win"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/anechoic_-4_10_4_clYODONUDFk8YpQ8.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "anechoic"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["lane", "lay", "late", "lake", "lace", "lame"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/noise_-9_4_5_6rm0GOB6RsDZVwjq.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-9", "condition": "noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["peel", "reel", "feel", "eel", "keel", "heel"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo_-4_27_2_sSlEP2eUYPtZt8Rh.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "echo"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["took", "cook", "look", "hook", "shook", "book"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/noise_-2_39_4_fkTvMnoTd0WfM7ic.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-2", "condition": "noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["mass", "math", "map", "mat", "man", "mad"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/sum_12_40_1_Zty57ZgzlPtuquBr.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "12", "condition": "sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["hold", "cold", "told", "fold", "sold", "gold"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/anechoic_14_2_3_6pzPYzpq6YObxMtV.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "anechoic"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["peace", "peas", "peak", "peach", "peat", "peal"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/anechoic_2_47_5_I4hGU63VnIYQAbY7.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "anechoic"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["went", "sent", "bent", "dent", "tent", "rent"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/ref_12_1_1_6nXkj1iQfApOjufz.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "12", "condition": "ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["cup", "cut", "cud", "cuff", "cuss", "cub"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-pitch_2_30_4_iMJsEcs60bKrprFM.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "echo-pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["shop", "mop", "cop", "top", "hop", "pop"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo_8_22_2_Fo68VJvE65NHz7xK.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "echo"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["tan", "tang", "tap", "tack", "tam", "tab"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo_-10_24_3_jOTSa1pnR5bJUtMl.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "echo"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["same", "name", "game", "tame", "came", "fame"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/pitch_12_26_2_iQKW4YdzvTilJ47S.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "12", "condition": "pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["hang", "sang", "bang", "rang", "fang", "gang"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/ref_6_38_4_Sfzv3ibD8NnCrr9m.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "6", "condition": "ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["sum", "sun", "sung", "sup", "sub", "sud"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-space_-4_12_1_jB3ZwL8zQx2SNaF9.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "echo-space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pen", "hen", "men", "then", "den", "ten"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/space_0_32_3_fYZwMAxszBiFolse.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "0", "condition": "space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["went", "sent", "bent", "dent", "tent", "rent"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-pitch_2_1_5_oG9xbmZuEMGHchCw.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "echo-pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["pat", "pad", "pan", "path", "pack", "pass"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/space_-6_3_6_HfWGgjr865B3gHw2.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-6", "condition": "space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["heat", "neat", "feat", "seat", "meat", "beat"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/pitch_12_35_4_xwpCiOt35R2K92Bs.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "12", "condition": "pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["kill", "kin", "kit", "kick", "king", "kid"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/noise_5_37_5_blI59mSNFnJYqBin.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "5", "condition": "noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["heat", "neat", "feat", "seat", "meat", "beat"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/pitch_6_35_5_R3Uobudw5xnRZUVZ.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "6", "condition": "pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["ray", "raze", "rate", "rave", "rake", "race"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-noise_0_41_4_n4GYDJJTNHcXGSc1.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "0", "condition": "echo-noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["vest", "test", "rest", "best", "west", "nest"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-ref_-10_15_5_0ccU28SRjh9kV3H1.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["bun", "bus", "but", "bug", "buck", "buff"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/noise_-9_48_6_svxLvNdGLYg9YBxf.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-9", "condition": "noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["save", "same", "sale", "sane", "sake", "safe"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/space_6_42_3_LldoN0U2IG2pHFzf.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "6", "condition": "space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["kit", "bit", "fit", "hit", "wit", "sit"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/space_-6_5_4_ZKAU34CPfZi1AHDE.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-6", "condition": "space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["kit", "bit", "fit", "hit", "wit", "sit"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-noise_-14_5_3_ENUxkzJEAjlEq5G5.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-14", "condition": "echo-noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["heat", "neat", "feat", "seat", "meat", "beat"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-sum_-4_35_5_u6mP03QqQlCZVk3b.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "echo-sum"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["way", "may", "say", "pay", "day", "gay"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/pitch_12_18_4_j6Me9QH6rNK2NVWP.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "12", "condition": "pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["mass", "math", "map", "mat", "man", "mad"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/noise_5_40_5_UWojkim4Mr6iCFKn.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "5", "condition": "noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["back", "bath", "bad", "bass", "bat", "ban"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/space_12_17_3_8O6vrkRNPPCv1dkB.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "12", "condition": "space"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["coil", "oil", "soil", "toil", "boil", "foil"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-noise_14_23_6_gsEXE0k5kStj3gbe.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo-noise"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["thaw", "law", "raw", "paw", "jaw", "saw"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-ref_8_31_2_hCWTDaPteUWcLfq3.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["heave", "hear", "heat", "heal", "heap", "heath"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-pitch_14_29_2_SA9dAlPX76A5HrOj.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo-pitch"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["not", "tot", "got", "pot", "hot", "lot"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-ref_14_14_2_Xreh2055wG7VFpcv.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["sill", "sick", "sip", "sing", "sit", "sin"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/main/echo-pitch_8_44_3_ZnLKXEK1g5dyUPVS.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "echo-pitch"}}]}